CHASON LAW

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

INFO

ADDRESS

1525 N MAIN ST #247, Bountiful, 84010

PHONE

305-799-0691

EMAIL

chasonthelaw@gmail.com

SKILLS

Great communication

Problem solving

Collaboration & Teamwork

Leadership

LANGUAGES

HTML

.

CSS

.

Javascript

.

React.js

 \bullet \bullet \circ \circ

Node.js

• • 0 0 0

MongoDB

• • 0 0 0

MySQL

• • 0 0 0

LINKS

github.com/chas0n2

linkedin.com/in/chason-law

chasonthelaw.com

PROFILE

Full Stack Web Developer with extensive experience in team coordination and management. Educated through the University of Utah in multiple front and back-end languages, such as Javascript, CSS, HTML, Node.js, and MongoDB - each language actively put to use in 6 months of team projects developing three web applications. Highly skilled in communication efforts, particularly when coordinating between departments, customers and team members.

EDUCATION

Full-Stack Web Development Program, University of Utah

Aug 2019 — Feb 2020

Learned and actively use Javascript, HTML, CSS, AJAX, NodeJS, MySQL, MongoDB with several other frameworks and JS libraries.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Senior Technical Support Specialist, Harvest Right

Mar 2017 — Present

|Train and lead 6-12, technical support agents, working alongside them in database navigation and customer support

| Improve CRM database functionality including workflow, bug reporting, and navigation, which has lead to the resolution of over 4500 tickets

| Coordinate customer relations using CRM reporting tools and call monitoring software

Lead Technician, Alder Protection

Orem

North Salt Lake

Feb 2013 — Dec 2017

| Instructed 12 security technicians over in-home and commercial security accounts

| Serviced accounts where products were installed, troubleshooting, and certifying installations

| Oversaw customer relations for all customers under my team and monitored over 2,200 customer accounts

Tier 2 Technical Support, Devcon Security

Orem

Jul 2011 — Apr 2012

 \mid Created sales orders, schedules, and reports through Oracle CRM software for over 60,000 customers

| Researched client needs to provide information and support for technicians

 $|\ \ \text{Advised technicians with installation and service of security systems}$

References available upon request